<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yue Deng</title>
    <link>https://yuedeng.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yue Deng</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://yuedeng.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://yuedeng.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 22:59:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuedeng.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a Ph.D. Candidate in Economics, from the Interdisciplinary Center for Economic Science at George Mason University. 
My primary fields of interest are behavioral and experimental economics, along with the secondary interests in health economics and industrial organization.
 Most commonly I investigate health behaviors, health epidemics and health market using laboratory, online or field experiments, as well as observational data to provide insights and policy implications for the real world.
 I love to follow my curiosities and be excited to find out where it leads me to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://yuedeng.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 22:20:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuedeng.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description> Job Market Paper  &amp;ldquo;Secondary Markets and the Opioid Crisis: Evidence from a Laboratory Experiment&amp;rdquo; with Daniel Houser
[abstract]  We study the effect of shutting down the secondary market on physicians' prescription behavior using a equilibrium model developed by Schnell and provide empirical knowledge through an lab experiment. The experiment isolates the effect on the physician-subjects' prescription behavior by controlling the anonymity of subjects and the availability of the secondary market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://yuedeng.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 22:08:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yuedeng.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>As instructor:  Introduction to Econometrics (Econ 345): Summer 2020 [syllabus]    As teaching assistant:  Behavioral Economics for Non-Profits (Econ 296): Summer 2018 [eval] [syllabus]</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
